<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><s:Envelope xmlns:s="http://www.w3.org/2003/05/soap-envelope" xmlns:a="http://www.w3.org/2005/08/addressing"><s:Header><a:Action s:mustUnderstand="1">http://TekTravel/HotelBookingApi/IHotelService/HotelCancellationPolicyResponse</a:Action></s:Header><s:Body xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema"><HotelCancellationPolicyResponse xmlns="http://TekTravel/HotelBookingApi"><Status><StatusCode>01</StatusCode><Description>Successful: HotelCancellationPolicy Successful</Description></Status><CancelPolicies PolicyFormat="Nodes"><LastCancellationDeadline>2021-09-23T00:00:00</LastCancellationDeadline><CancelPolicy FromDate="2021-04-07" ToDate="2021-09-23" ChargeType="Fixed" CancellationCharge="0" Currency="USD"/><CancelPolicy FromDate="2021-09-24" ToDate="2021-09-25" ChargeType="Percentage" CancellationCharge="100" Currency="USD"/><DefaultPolicy>Early check out will attract full cancellation charge unless otherwise specified</DefaultPolicy><AutoCancellationText>Hotel Destination Local Date and Time:23-Sep-2021,21:30:00</AutoCancellationText></CancelPolicies><HotelNorms><string>CheckIn Time-Begin: 3:00 PM </string><string> CheckIn Time-End: midnight</string><string>CheckOut Time: 12:00 PM</string><string>CheckIn Instructions: &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on property policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card, debit card, or cash deposit may be required at check-in for incidental charges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges; special requests cannot be guaranteed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This property accepts credit cards; cash is not accepted&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Noise-free guestrooms cannot be guaranteed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Safety features at this property include a carbon monoxide detector, a fire extinguisher, a smoke detector, a security system, a first aid kit, and window guards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Please note that cultural norms and guest policies may differ by country and by property; the policies listed are provided by the property&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt; </string><string> Special Instructions : Front desk staff will greet guests on arrival. For more details, please contact the property using the information on the booking confirmation.  Due to COVID-19, this property's food and beverage options may be limited pursuant to local regulations.</string><string>Minimum CheckIn Age : 21</string><string>Mandatory Fees: &lt;p&gt;You'll be asked to pay the following charges at the property:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;8 percent destination fee will be charged&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;We have included all charges provided to us by the property. &lt;/p&gt; </string><string> Optional Fees: &lt;p&gt;The following fees and deposits are charged by the property at time of service, check-in, or check-out. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Breakfast fee: between USD 7 and USD 15 per person (approximately)&lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;Self parking fee: USD 10.00 per night&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Pet fee: USD 75 per pet, per stay&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Service animals are exempt from fees&lt;/li&gt;      &lt;li&gt;Rollaway bed fee: USD 10 per night&lt;/li&gt;            &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;The above list may not be comprehensive. Fees and deposits may not include tax and are subject to change. &lt;/p&gt;</string><string>Cards Accepted: Visa,Debit cards not accepted,Cash not accepted,Discover,American Express,Mastercard,UnionPay</string><string>&lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;The property has connecting/adjoining rooms, which are subject to availability and can be requested by contacting the property using the number on the booking confirmation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This property allows pets in specific rooms only (surcharges apply and can be found in the Fees section). Guests can request one of these rooms by contacting the property directly, using the contact information on the booking confirmation. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;This property advises that enhanced cleaning and guest safety measures are currently in place.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Disinfectant is used to clean the property; commonly-touched surfaces are cleaned with disinfectant between stays; bed sheets and towels are laundered at a temperature of at least 60째C/140째F.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Social distancing measures are in place; staff at the property wear personal protective equipment; a shield is in place between staff and guests in main contact areas; periodic temperature checks are conducted on staff; guests are provided with hand sanitizer; masks are required in public areas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contactless check-in and contactless check-out are available.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Individually-wrapped food options are available for breakfast.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This property affirms that it follows the cleaning and disinfection practices of We Care Clean (Best Western).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This property affirms that it adheres to the cleaning and disinfection practices of SafeStay (AHLA - USA).&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;For details on Best Western's privacy policy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.bestwestern.com/privacy" target="_blank"&gt;www.bestwestern.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;,Pet maximum weight in lb is 65,Maximum number of pets per room 1,Pet maximum weight in kg is 29,Service animals are allowed,Service animals are exempt from fees/restrictions,Only dogs are allowed,Pets allowed,Property follows a brand or regulatory agency's sanitization guidelines We Care Clean (Best Western),Shield between guests and staff in main contact areas,Contactless check-out is available,Property confirms they are implementing guest safety measures,Social distancing measures are in place,Individually-wrapped food options are available,Property follows sanitization practices of SafeStay (AHLA - USA),Staff temperature checks are conducted regularly,Property is cleaned with disinfectant,Guests are provided with free hand sanitizer,Property confirms they are implementing enhanced cleaning measures,Noise-free rooms not guaranteed,Staff wears personal protective equipment,Individually-wrapped food options are available for breakfast,Bed sheets and towels are washed at a temperature of at least 60째C/140째F,Essential Workers Only - NO,Contactless check-in is available,Masks are compulsory at the property,No cribs (infant beds) available,Commonly-touched surfaces are cleaned with disinfectant</string></HotelNorms></HotelCancellationPolicyResponse></s:Body></s:Envelope>